(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(Ver en www.dramacool.club Administrador de soporte)
Hey, who are you?
Hola, ¿quién eres?
You fucking bastard! Actually, actually, you know what?
¡Maldito bastardo! En realidad, en realidad, ¿sabes qué?
Forget it.
Olvídalo.
I don't really care who you are. It doesn't matter.
Realmente no me importa quién seas. No importa.
And I won't try to find out, either.
Y yo tampoco intentaré averiguarlo.
Just give me back the van. Turn around and come back.
Devuélveme la furgoneta. Date la vuelta y regresa.
I'm gonna find you tonight anyway.
De todas formas, te encontraré esta noche.
Then you're done.
Entonces ya has terminado.
HAPPY! GANGWON
¡FELIZ! GANGWON
EPISODE 1 BETTING
EPISODIO 1 APUESTAS
Hi there. Is the captain at home?
Hola. ¿Está el capitán en casa?
Oh, he's away for work right now.
Oh, ahora mismo está fuera por trabajo.
Oh, is that right?
¿Ah, sí?
It's just, well, the rent. It's really overdue.
Es que, bueno, el alquiler. Está muy atrasado.
It's been over three months now, right?
Ya han pasado más de tres meses, ¿verdad?
You know, we're not just talking about one or two months.
Ya sabes, no estamos hablando solo de uno o dos meses.
We're talking about three months.
Estamos hablando de tres meses.
Look, if he's going through something, I understand, but...
Mira, si está pasando por algo, lo entiendo, pero...
He could at least tell me what's going on.
Al menos podría decirme qué está pasando.
Instead, he ignores all my calls and my texts.
En cambio, ignora todas mis llamadas y mis mensajes de texto.
You two aren't having any problems or anything, are you?
Ustedes dos no tienen ningún problema ni nada, ¿verdad?
I know I shouldn't say this to you.
Sé que no debería decirte esto.
Tell him for me?
¿Díselo por mí?
CONNECTING CALL... DOKYUNG
CONECTANDO LLAMADA... DOKYUNG
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice messaging...
Su llamada ha sido desviada a un sistema de mensajería de voz automatizado...
YOU'RE COMING TODAY, RIGHT?
¿Vienes hoy, verdad?
You're going to absolutely love this trip.
Este viaje te va a encantar.
THE LANDLADY CAME BY ABOUT THE RENT.
LA CASERA VINO A HABLAR SOBRE EL ALQUILER.
Home to the Mona Lisa. This is the best that Europe has to offer.
Hogar de la Mona Lisa. Esto es lo mejor que Europa tiene para ofrecer.
TRAVEL SAFE. SEE YOU LATER
¡Buen viaje! ¡Hasta luego!
Enjoy an easy, rewarding, and comfortable experience.
Disfrute de una experiencia fácil, gratificante y cómoda.
And for those of you...
Y para aquellos de ustedes...
00 O'CLOCK
00 EN PUNTO
I'm sorry but this card was declined.
Lo siento, pero esta tarjeta ha sido rechazada.
Are you sure?
¿Está seguro?
Could you just try it one more time, please?
¿Podrías intentarlo una vez más, por favor?
It's not going through.
No se está procesando.
Uh, how much is the total?
Eh, ¿cuánto es el total?
Welcome.
Bienvenido.
Please press the number of the transaction you would like to complete.
Por favor, pulse el número de la transacción que desea completar.
Please enter the amount you...
Por favor, introduzca la cantidad que...
- INSUFFICIENT ACCOUNT BALANCE. - KRW 0.
- SALDO INSUFICIENTE EN LA CUENTA. - KRW 0.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR AVAILABLE BALANCE BEFORE PROCEEDING WITH THE TRANSACTION.
POR FAVOR, VERIFIQUE SU SALDO DISPONIBLE ANTES DE PROCEDER CON LA TRANSACCIÓN.
Please take your card.
Por favor, tome su tarjeta.
YOU'RE COMING TODAY, RIGHT? TRAVEL SAFE. SEE YOU LATER
¿Vienes hoy, verdad? ¡ Buen viaje! ¡Hasta luego!
See you soon. I love you.
Hasta pronto. Te quiero.
Love you.
Te amo.
INTERNATIONAL ARRIVALS
LLEGADAS INTERNACIONALES
A404 THAILAND/SUVARNABHUMI 15:00 ARRIVED
A404 TAILANDIA/SUVARNABHUMI 15:00 LLEGADA
Attention, passengers.
Atención, pasajeros.
Final boarding call for flight 407 to Tokyo.
Último llamado a abordar el vuelo 407 con destino a Tokio.
Hi. I have a question. Do you know this woman?
Hola. Tengo una pregunta. ¿Conoces a esta mujer?
She works here.
Ella trabaja aquí.
Yes, we were able to make note
Sí, pudimos tomar nota.
of this shipment but we still have...
de este envío pero aún tenemos...
X-WHEN THE EQUIPMENT IS IN OPERATION,
X-CUANDO EL EQUIPO ESTÉ EN FUNCIONAMIENTO,
DO NOT PLACE ANY PART OF YOUR BODY INSIDE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
NO INTRODUZCA NINGUNA PARTE DE SU CUERPO EN EL INTERIOR BAJO NINGUNA CIRCUNSTANCIA
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
PROHIBIDA LA ENTRADA SIN AUTORIZACIÓN
Belt two, unload the cargo.
Cinta transportadora dos, descarga la mercancía.
Which one is it?
¿Cuál es?
That's right!
¡Así es!
Aren't you off this weekend?
¿No tienes el fin de semana libre?
We're all going to Sokcho to check out this hot new night club.
Todos vamos a ir a Sokcho para conocer esta nueva discoteca de moda.
You should come with us!
¡Deberías venir con nosotros!
I've got things to do at home.
Tengo cosas que hacer en casa.
Oh, come on. No, you don't.
¡Ay, por favor! No, no lo harás.
You can't just be cooped up here all the time.
No puedes estar encerrado aquí todo el tiempo.
You gotta go out and have fun, too.
Tú también tienes que salir y divertirte.
Sorry, guys. I'll join you on the next one.
Lo siento, chicos. Me uno a vosotros en el próximo vídeo.
She plays hard to get, doesn't she?
Se hace la difícil, ¿verdad?
You're not here to fool around.
No estás aquí para perder el tiempo.
Not without me, you aren't.
Sin mí, no lo eres.
Of course you have to come with us!
¡Por supuesto que tienes que venir con nosotros!
Where would we go without you?
¿Adónde iríamos sin ti?
So where are we going?
¿Adónde vamos entonces?
We're gonna go clubbing, duh!
¡Vamos a ir de fiesta, obvio!
Wait, Heeju.
Espera, Heeju.
-Can we talk for a minute? -Oh, okay.
-¿Podemos hablar un minuto? -Oh, de acuerdo.
Earlier today...
Hoy temprano...
This guy came by and said he was your uncle.
Este hombre vino y dijo que era tu tío.
He showed me an old school photo of you and asked if I knew you.
Me enseñó una foto antigua tuya del colegio y me preguntó si te conocía.
He said that an acquaintance of his saw you working here in your security uniform.
Dijo que un conocido suyo te vio trabajando aquí con tu uniforme de seguridad.
So what did you tell him?
¿Y qué le dijiste?
That no one here looks like that.
Que aquí nadie se parece a eso.
If he doesn't know, there's gotta be a reason, right?
Si no lo sabe, tiene que haber una razón, ¿verdad?
Is he really your uncle?
¿De verdad es tu tío?
No, he's not.
No, no lo es.
I thought so.
Ya me lo imaginaba.
He just seems kinda odd.
Simplemente parece un poco raro.
Who was he?
¿Quién era él?
Did you get mixed up with a loan shark?
¿Te has visto envuelto en problemas con un usurero?
Uh, no. It's nothing like that.
Eh, no. No es nada de eso.
Then who was it?
¿Entonces quién era?
Tell me and maybe I can help you.
Cuéntame y tal vez pueda ayudarte.
You hardly ever talk about yourself.
Casi nunca hablas de ti mismo.
I'm sorry. Can I ask...
Lo siento. ¿Puedo preguntar...?
If that man ever comes back, could you tell him I don't work here?
Si ese hombre regresa alguna vez, ¿ podrías decirle que no trabajo aquí?
I can do that.
Puedo hacerlo.
Just be careful outside of work, too.
Ten cuidado también fuera del trabajo.
Word of advice.
Un consejo.
If you didn't do anything wrong, don't run away.
Si no hiciste nada malo, no huyas.
Once you start running from guys like him, you'll end up running your whole life.
Una vez que empieces a huir de tipos como él, acabarás huyendo toda tu vida.
Yes.
Sí.
I appreciate it, ma'am.
Se lo agradezco, señora.
What do you guys want?
¿Qué es lo que queréis?
You just had to come all this way here to find me? Really?
¿Tenías que venir hasta aquí para encontrarme? ¿En serio?
You're a difficult man to reach.
Eres un hombre difícil de contactar.
Look, I always repay Geumseong back, don't I?
Mira, siempre le devuelvo el favor a Geumseong, ¿no?
I heard it's been a year.
He oído que ha pasado un año.
Let's talk it over in Jeongsan.
Hablemos de ello en Jeongsan.
Well, let's say you go back to Jeongsan now.
Bueno, digamos que ahora regresas a Jeongsan.
The boys here will have to clean you out.
Los chicos de aquí tendrán que dejarte sin nada.
Your organs. They're healthy, right?
Tus órganos. Están sanos, ¿verdad?
What?
¿Qué?
It's a joke, man. A joke.
Es una broma, tío. Una broma.
We wouldn't do that to you.
Nosotros no te haríamos eso.
We'll be partners.
Seremos socios.
Forever and ever.
Por los siglos de los siglos.
What do you want me to do now?
¿Qué quieres que haga ahora?
Hold your questions.
Guarden sus preguntas.
First up, we need to check your collateral.
En primer lugar, necesitamos comprobar su garantía.
Where have you been?
¿Dónde has estado?
I'm still in Bangkok.
Todavía estoy en Bangkok.
What?
¿Qué?
-What are you still doing there? -I'll tell you later.
—¿Qué sigues haciendo ahí? —Te lo diré después.
Where are you now? Are you home?
¿Dónde estás ahora? ¿ Estás en casa?
Yeah. I just walked in.
Sí. Acabo de entrar.
Get out of the house right now, Heeju.
Sal de la casa ahora mismo, Heeju.
What? Why?
¿Qué? ¿Por qué?
There's no time. Just get out right now.
No hay tiempo. Sal de aquí ahora mismo.
Grab whatever you need, clothes, photos, and get out of there.
Coge lo que necesites, ropa, fotos, y sal de ahí.
Some people are headed over there right now.
Hay gente que se dirige hacia allá ahora mismo.
They can't know that you're there.
No pueden saber que estás ahí.
Some people? Who?
¿Algunas personas? ¿Quiénes?
There's no time to explain! Just go!
¡No hay tiempo para explicaciones! ¡Vete ya!
-Call me after you've left. -What are you talking about?
-Llámame después de que te hayas ido. -¿De qué estás hablando?
H-hello?
¿H-hola?
Pictures.
Fotos.
Oh, my passport.
Oh, mi pasaporte.
Got it.
Entiendo.
What the fuck? Someone lives here.
¿Qué coño? Aquí vive alguien.
Ah, dammit.
¡Ah, maldita sea!
Hello? Is anyone here?
¿Hola? ¿Hay alguien aquí?
Look around. What is this?
Mira a tu alrededor. ¿Qué es esto?
-Go check the balcony. -Ah, shit.
-Ve a revisar el balcón. -Ah, mierda.
Nothing here.
Aquí no hay nada.
You checked everything?
¿Lo has comprobado todo?
Ah, shit. Where the hell are they, dammit?
Ah, mierda. ¿Dónde diablos están, maldita sea?
Did you go in there?
¿Entraste ahí?
-Heeju, where are you right now? -I'm on the bus.
-Heeju, ¿dónde estás ahora mismo? -Estoy en el autobús.
You need to tell me what's going on.
Necesitas decirme qué está pasando.
What do those people want with you?
¿Qué quieren esas personas de ti?
Don't worry about them. It's nothing.
No te preocupes por ellos. No es nada.
You don't think it's a big deal that a group of strange men
No crees que sea gran cosa que un grupo de hombres extraños
just barged in through the door?
¿Simplemente irrumpió por la puerta?
Talk to me. What's going on?
Háblame. ¿Qué está pasando?
I already told you it's okay.
Ya te dije que está bien.
You don't need to worry about it.
No tienes que preocuparte por eso.
Your credit card has been frozen,
Tu tarjeta de crédito ha sido bloqueada.
and I learned your rent is overdue by three months.
Y me enteré de que tienes el alquiler atrasado tres meses.
The landlady came by asking for you.
La casera vino preguntando por ti.
Dokyung, are you still gambling?
Dokyung, ¿sigues apostando?
Did you use a loan shark?
¿Recurriste a un prestamista usurero?
Yeah, I went to a casino with my friends last year.
Sí, fui a un casino con mis amigos el año pasado.
How much?
¿Cuánto cuesta?
I have a little bit of money saved.
Tengo un poco de dinero ahorrado.
It wasn't much. And I paid it off.
No era mucho. Y lo pagué.
Then why did those people come?
Entonces, ¿por qué vinieron esas personas?
I just paid them back now.
Acabo de devolverles el dinero.
Well then, can I just go back?
Bueno, entonces, ¿puedo simplemente regresar?
No, stay at a hotel. I'll be there tomorrow.
No, quédate en un hotel. Yo estaré allí mañana.
I know I was supposed to be back today.
Sé que se suponía que debía estar de vuelta hoy.
But there were some complications that came up.
Pero surgieron algunas complicaciones .
Basically, this chairman I know who lives in Cambodia.
Básicamente, conozco a este presidente que vive en Camboya.
He's Korean.
Él es coreano.
And one of his employees actually passed away in
Y uno de sus empleados falleció en
an accident over here.
Un accidente por aquí.
We need to ship his body back to Korea by tomorrow.
Necesitamos enviar su cuerpo de regreso a Corea mañana mismo.
But you know how that stuff can be complicated.
Pero ya sabes lo complicado que puede ser ese tipo de cosas.
So he called me to ask if I could help out.
Así que me llamó para preguntarme si podía ayudarle.
I see. Are you sure everything's okay?
Ya veo. ¿Estás seguro de que todo está bien?
Nothing will happen to us, right?
No nos pasará nada, ¿verdad?
Everything will be fine. Just trust me.
Todo saldrá bien. Confía en mí.
But Heeju?
¿Pero Heeju?
I do have one small favor to ask.
Tengo un pequeño favor que pedirte.
The, uh, casket, the one I'm shipping tomorrow...
El, eh, ataúd, el que envío mañana...
Would you be able to handle the airport security check?
¿Podrías superar el control de seguridad del aeropuerto?
I'm off tomorrow.
Mañana tengo el día libre.
But you can swap shifts with someone.
Pero puedes intercambiar turnos con alguien.
I need you to make sure the casket gets past the checkpoint, okay?
Necesito que te asegures de que el ataúd pase el control de seguridad, ¿de acuerdo?
And if the scanners should see something, just let it through.
Y si los escáneres detectan algo, simplemente déjenlo pasar.
Why? What's in it?
¿Por qué? ¿Qué contiene?
I'm just saying, in case something goes wrong.
Lo digo por si acaso algo sale mal.
Okay. What could go wrong?
Vale. ¿Qué podría salir mal?
Nothing.
Nada.
Trust me, Heeju.
Confía en mí, Heeju.
Do what I tell you to do.
Haz lo que te digo.
Shoot, the chairman is here.
¡Caramba, el presidente está aquí!
I need to go. Please don't forget.
Tengo que irme. Por favor, no lo olvides.
Flight A404.
Vuelo A404.
It's departing from Siem Riep at 7:00 A.M. tomorrow, 'kay?
Sale de Siem Reap mañana a las 7:00 AM, ¿de acuerdo?
Love you.
Te amo.
Yeah, love you-
Sí, te quiero.
-Hi, you guys. -Hi, Heeju!
-Hola, chicos. -¡Hola, Heeju!
-Hi. -Come on. Just ask her.
-Hola. -Vamos. Solo pregúntale.
Weren't you off today?
¿No tenías el día libre hoy?
Uh, Yerim and I changed shifts.
Eh, Yerim y yo cambiamos de turno.
Really? Why? Is she okay?
¿En serio? ¿Por qué? ¿Está bien?
I don't know.
No sé.
Weird. It's not like her to miss a shift.
Qué raro. No es propio de ella faltar a su turno.
Right? Have you heard anything?
¿Verdad? ¿Has oído algo?
RADIATION CONTROLLED AREA
ZONA CONTROLADA DE RADIACIÓN
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
PROHIBIDA LA ENTRADA SIN AUTORIZACIÓN
What's going on with belt two?
¿Qué está pasando con la segunda cinta transportadora?
It's all the metal decorations attached to the casket.
Son todas las decoraciones metálicas que están adheridas al ataúd.
Heeju.
Ey.
Let it go through.
Déjalo pasar.
Okay.
Bueno.
One, two, three.
Uno, dos, tres.
Long time no see, Captain.
¡Cuánto tiempo sin verte, Capitán!
You haven't been to Gold Land much these days, have you?
Últimamente no has ido mucho a Gold Land , ¿verdad?
You've been up to somethin' big.
Has estado tramando algo grande.
If you need any dough, just let me know and I can help you out.
Si necesitas dinero, avísame y te ayudaré.
What am I saying?
¿Qué estoy diciendo?
You don't need petty cash from grunts like us.
No necesitas dinero en efectivo de simples peones como nosotros.
Sorry.
Lo siento.
The hell is this?
¿Qué demonios es esto?
What's it look like? It's a gun.
¿Qué aspecto tiene? Es una pistola.
A real gun.
Un arma de verdad.
It's fully loaded. Wanna check?
Está totalmente cargado. ¿Quieres comprobarlo?
What?
¿Qué?
Look. Look, that exit on the right.
Mira. Mira, esa salida a la derecha.
I need you to get off there.
Necesito que te bajes de ahí.
Captain, why are you...
Capitán, ¿por qué está usted...?
Hey, fucking hell! Hold the wheel! Hands on the fucking wheel!
¡Oye, maldita sea! ¡Sujeta el volante! ¡Manos en el maldito volante!
Listen, we're gonna take the next exit.
Escucha, vamos a tomar la siguiente salida.
-Just take the fucking exit. -We can't-we can't do this.
-Simplemente toma la maldita salida. -No podemos, no podemos hacer esto.
I said take the fucking exit, man!
¡Te dije que tomaras la maldita salida, hombre!
What the fuck? Where are they going?
¿Qué carajo? ¿ Adónde van?
Who the fuck is driving?
¿Quién diablos está conduciendo?
Woogy, sir.
Woogy, señor.
Shit.
Mierda.
BOSS
JEFE
Hey. Eyes on the road. Keep going.
Oye. Mira en la carretera. Sigue adelante.
I said just focus on driving, you fucking dumb ass!
¡Te dije que te concentraras en conducir, maldito idiota!
Oh, fuck.
Oh, joder.
Get the fuck out, you asshole.
¡Lárgate de aquí, imbécil!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait. -What?
-¡Alto, alto, alto, espera, espera! -¿Qué?
Can I at least have my phone? Please?
¿Al menos puedo tener mi teléfono? ¿Por favor?
Yeah. Call them.
Sí. Llámalos.
Shit.
Mierda.
Fuckin' asshole! Fuck you, man!
¡Maldito imbécil! ¡ Que te jodan, tío!
What's going on?
¿Qué está sucediendo?
You even called in the boys.
Incluso llamaste a los chicos.
We gotta take care of some meat.
Tenemos que ocuparnos de algo de carne.
A debtor?
¿Un deudor?
Just cutting off parts or butchering?
¿Simplemente cortar partes o descuartizar?
Butcher as usual.
Carnicero como siempre.
Strip him clean and hand it all over.
Desnúdalo por completo y entrégalo todo.
We aren't really prepared for that.
Realmente no estamos preparados para eso.
You could have warned us.
Podrías habernos avisado.
-Hey, Seokgu! -Yes, boss.
-¡Oye, Seokgu! -Sí, jefe.
Call Mr. Jin and tell him to come over.
Llama al Sr. Jin y dile que venga.
-Tell him don't forget his tools. -Right away, boss. Yes.
-Dígale que no olvide sus herramientas. -Enseguida, jefe. Sí.
Who's that?
¿Quién es ese?
INCOMING CALL CAPTAIN LEE DOKYUNG
LLAMADA ENTRANTE CAPITÁN LEE DOKYUNG
Hey, Captain. Have you arrived yet?
Hola, capitán. ¿ Ya has llegado?
Where you at?
¿Dónde estás?
Oh, I guess they haven't let you know.
Oh, supongo que no te lo han dicho.
I'm the one driving the funeral van now.
Ahora soy yo quien conduce la furgoneta fúnebre.
And I managed to shake off all your men.
Y logré deshacerme de todos tus hombres.
The casket is safe, so don't worry about that.
El ataúd está a salvo, así que no te preocupes por eso.
Captain.
Capitán.
What exactly are you saying?
¿Qué es exactamente lo que estás diciendo?
I owe Yes Money two hundred million won, right?
Le debo doscientos millones de wones a Yes Money, ¿verdad?
You agree to write it off if I help move the casket.
Aceptas deducirlo si te ayudo a mover el ataúd.
212 million.
212 millones.
Well, close enough.
Bueno, casi.
I'm sorry to say, I don't think that's gonna cut it.
Lamento decirlo, pero no creo que eso sea suficiente.
Also, you really don't want me hanging around in Korea, right?
Además, no querrás que me quede por Corea, ¿verdad?
I want a billion won in cash.
Quiero mil millones de wones en efectivo.
Then I'll return the casket and quietly disappear.
Entonces devolveré el ataúd y desapareceré discretamente.
I noticed it was pretty heavy.
Me di cuenta de que era bastante pesado.
That's a lot of drugs. Must be worth at least 10 billion.
Son muchísimas drogas. Deben valer al menos 10 mil millones.
I'm risking my life to transport this thing.
Estoy arriesgando mi vida para transportar esta cosa.
I want ten percent.
Quiero el diez por ciento.
Not a bad deal for shipping cost, right?
No está mal para el costo de envío, ¿verdad?
You made yourself very clear.
Te explicaste con mucha claridad.
This is gonna take some time, though.
Esto va a llevar algún tiempo.
I gotta get approval from the chairman first.
Primero tengo que obtener la aprobación del presidente.
Then we have to prepare the cash.
Luego tenemos que preparar el dinero en efectivo.
You can have up until midnight.
Puedes tenerlo hasta la medianoche.
I'll be waiting at Geumsong.
Estaré esperando en Geumsong.
First I'll check the cash.
Primero revisaré el efectivo.
And then I'll give you the location of the van.
Y luego te daré la ubicación de la furgoneta.
Okay. Let's do that.
De acuerdo. Hagámoslo.
Fuckin' bastard!
¡Maldito bastardo!
Kim Jinman, Jeongsan Police Investigations.
Kim Jinman, Investigaciones de la Policía de Jeongsan.
It's Park Hocheol.
Es Park Hocheol.
I need you to track a phone for me.
Necesito que rastrees un teléfono por mí.
Whose phone? What for?
¿De quién es el teléfono? ¿Para qué?
That's none of your business. You got until midnight.
Eso no te incumbe. Tienes hasta medianoche.
Oh, come on.
¡Ay, por favor!
You know that's not the kind of thing I can do so easily.
Sabes que no es algo que pueda hacer con tanta facilidad.
I mean, I have to get a warrant and everything.
Quiero decir, tengo que conseguir una orden judicial y todo eso.
It'd be illegal without one.
Sería ilegal sin uno.
It involves the Chairman.
Esto involucra al Presidente.
Name and phone number.
Nombre y número de teléfono.
Lee Dokyung.
Lee Dokyung.
MOBILE PHONE DOKYUNG
TELÉFONO MÓVIL DOKYUNG
Hello?
¿Hola?
Heeju. Heeju.
Jeje. Jeje.
-Dokyung. -Heeju.
-Dokyung. -Heeju.
Get in.
Entra.
Oh, Heeju!
¡Oh, Heeju!
It's okay. It's okay.
Está bien. Está bien.
You must have been scared.
Debes haber estado asustado.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
It's all right.
Está bien.
-You left your phone, right? -Mm-hmm.
-Dejaste tu teléfono, ¿verdad? -Mm-hmm.
From now on we only use these, okay?
De ahora en adelante solo usaremos estos, ¿de acuerdo?
I need you to listen to me very carefully, Heeju.
Necesito que me escuches con mucha atención, Heeju.
I'm gonna go meet up with someone right now.
Voy a reunirme con alguien ahora mismo.
They're gonna give me some money.
Me van a dar algo de dinero.
It's a lot.
Es mucho.
Enough for us to leave this place for good.
Es suficiente para que nos vayamos de este lugar para siempre.
A billion won.
Mil millones de wones.
-Huh? -I'll be right back, okay?
-¿Eh? -Vuelvo enseguida, ¿vale?
You stay here and wait in the van.
Quédate aquí y espera en la furgoneta.
Then when I call you on this phone,
Entonces, cuando te llame por este teléfono,
all you have to do is bring the van to the place I tell you.
Lo único que tienes que hacer es traer la furgoneta al lugar que te diga.
Wait, what-what are you talking...
Espera, ¿de qué estás hablando...?
It's not far. Just listen to me!
No está lejos. ¡ Solo escúchame!
If I don't...
Si no lo hago...
If you haven't received a call from me by midnight,
Si no has recibido una llamada mía antes de medianoche,
then take this van and run away.
Entonces, coge esta furgoneta y huye.
And ditch the phone.
Y deshazte del teléfono.
As long as you have that casket, they won't be able to hurt me.
As long as you have that casket, they won't be able to hurt me.
Who are you meeting with?
Who are you meeting with?
And what the hell is in that thing?
And what the hell is in that thing?
-Seriously, just tell me what's going on! -It'll all be over soon.
-Seriously, just tell me what's going on! -It'll all be over soon.
-You don't need to know about this, Heeju. -Why?
-You don't need to know about this, Heeju. -Why?
What aren't you telling me?
What aren't you telling me?
Dokyung.
Dokyung.
Listen, I will do exactly as you say.
Listen, I will do exactly as you say.
That's exactly why I need to know.
That's exactly why I need to know.
What am I doing and why?
What am I doing and why?
I'll explain everything later.
I'll explain everything later.
When it's over,
When it's over,
the two of us should go to France.
the two of us should go to France.
A fresh start. We'll forget all this.
A fresh start. We'll forget all this.
We can finally be happy. Okay?
We can finally be happy. Okay?
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you.
Please.
Please.
Thank you.
Thank you.
I'll be back. Just be careful.
I'll be back. Just be careful.
Shit.
Shit.
He must be dead, right?
He must be dead, right?
I hit him pretty damn hard.
I hit him pretty damn hard.
Hey! Go over and search every inch of the place!
Hey! Go over and search every inch of the place!
It's there somewhere.
It's there somewhere.
-Get going! Run! -Ah, fuck.
-Get going! Run! -Ah, fuck.
Hurry up.
Hurry up.
-Run away, Heeju. -Dokyung.
-Run away, Heeju. -Dokyung.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What? No, no, no. Dokyung, are you there?
What? No, no, no. Dokyung, are you there?
Please don't go!
Please don't go!
Don't...
Don't...
Sir, I found the van.
Sir, I found the van.
Yeah, it's in the warehouse at the top on the right.
Yeah, it's in the warehouse at the top on the right.
Okay, you stay put.
Okay, you stay put.
Hey, boss!
Hey, boss!
They found the van!
They found the van!
We need the keys! Check and see if the keys are with him.
We need the keys! Check and see if the keys are with him.
No keys here!
No keys here!
Someone's in the van!
Someone's in the van!
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Hey, block the van! Hurry! Move it! Move it!
Hey, block the van! Hurry! Move it! Move it!
-Fuck. -Boss! What the...
-Fuck. -Boss! What the...
Fuck!
Fuck!
Shit.
Shit.
Hey, who are you?
Hey, who are you?
You fucking bastard.
You fucking bastard.
Ah, actually, actually, you know what? Forget it.
Ah, actually, actually, you know what? Forget it.
I don't really care who you are. It doesn't matter.
I don't really care who you are. It doesn't matter.
And I won't try to find out, either.
And I won't try to find out, either.
Just give me back the van. Turn around and come back.
Just give me back the van. Turn around and come back.
You can have the money I promised Dokyung.
You can have the money I promised Dokyung.
I can send it right away.
I can send it right away.
If you haven't received a call from me by midnight,
If you haven't received a call from me by midnight,
then I need you to take this van and run away.
then I need you to take this van and run away.
And ditch this phone.
And ditch this phone.
As long as you have that casket, they won't be able to hurt me.
As long as you have that casket, they won't be able to hurt me.
You can't hide from me, you stupid fuck,
You can't hide from me, you stupid fuck,
so just hand it over!
so just hand it over!
I'm gonna find you tonight anyway.
I'm gonna find you tonight anyway.
Then you're done.
Then you're done.
Your call has been forwarded
Your call has been forwarded
to an automated voice messaging system.
to an automated voice messaging system.
The number you have dialed is not available.
The number you have dialed is not available.
Son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Why did it have to be here?
Why did it have to be here?
DAD! BE SAFE AGAIN TODAY
DAD! BE SAFE AGAIN TODAY
I thought I'd never see this place again.
I thought I'd never see this place again.
At first, I didn't expect my path would be like this.
At first, I didn't expect my path would be like this.
I only wanted to escape from my miserable and unhappy life.
I only wanted to escape from my miserable and unhappy life.
Get away from it all.
Get away from it all.
I was just following this small ray of light I saw before me.
I was just following this small ray of light I saw before me.
Hoping that if only I could reach it...
Con la esperanza de poder alcanzarlo...
...I could escape from all this darkness.
...podría escapar de toda esta oscuridad.
Mongsil, wait!
¡Mongsil, espera!
Mongsil?
¿Mongsil?
Mongsil!
¡Mongsil!
Mongsil, here!
¡Mongsil, aquí!
Heeju.
Ey.
Mongsil.
Mongol.
Where are you?
¿Dónde estás?
PROCEED SLOWLY
PROCEDA LENTAMENTE
Mongsil?
¿Mongsil?
Are you there?
¿Está ahí?
Mongsil.
Mongol.
Mommy.
Mami.
Heeju.
Ey.
Hurry up now.
Date prisa.
You have to run away from here.
Tienes que huir de aquí.
I'm still not sure what I saw back then.
Todavía no estoy seguro de qué fue lo que vi en aquel entonces.
Was it all a dream?
¿Fue todo un sueño?
Or was it a memory I made up for myself when I grew up?
¿O fue un recuerdo que me inventé al crecer?
RESTRICTED AREA
ZONA RESTRINGIDA
PROCEED SLOWLY
PROCEDA LENTAMENTE
COMPLY AND DRIVE SLOWLY
CUMPLE Y CONDUCE DESPACIO
INCLINED SHAFT 8, SECTION 2 102ML
EJE INCLINADO 8, SECCIÓN 2 102ML
How did it all end up like this?
¿Cómo hemos llegado a esta situación?
Happy. That's all I ever wanted.
Feliz. Eso es todo lo que siempre quise.
To be happy like everyone else.
Ser feliz como todos los demás.
As long as you have that casket, they won't be able to hurt me.
Mientras tengas ese ataúd, no podrán hacerme daño.
I need you to take this van and run away.
Necesito que cojas esta furgoneta y huyas.
If I hadn't come here that day...
Si no hubiera venido aquí ese día...
If I hadn't seen those gold bars inside that casket,
Si no hubiera visto esas barras de oro dentro de ese ataúd,
would I have been happy?
¿Habría sido feliz?
Or would my life be the same, dark as always,
¿O mi vida seguiría siendo la misma, oscura como siempre?
just like that mine shaft?
¿Igual que ese pozo de mina?